<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="it-IT"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://vittoriomigliore.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://vittoriomigliore.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="it-IT" /><updated>2023-10-10T03:07:58+02:00</updated><id>https://vittoriomigliore.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Vittorio Migliore</title><subtitle>Developer</subtitle><entry><title type="html">A Personal Wiki-Blog</title><link href="https://vittoriomigliore.github.io/a-personal-wiki-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Personal Wiki-Blog" /><published>2022-10-09T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2022-10-09T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>https://vittoriomigliore.github.io/a-personal-wiki-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://vittoriomigliore.github.io/a-personal-wiki-blog/">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my personal wiki-blog, a dynamic platform where I document and share my ongoing learning process and my knowledge. In this article, I’d like to introduce you to this unique fusion of a personal blog and a wiki, designed to capture my educational adventures and growth.
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-learning-wiki-blog-a-nexus-of-exploration&quot;&gt;The Learning Wiki-Blog: A Nexus of Exploration&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A learning wiki-blog combines the best of both worlds—a blog’s personal touch and a wiki’s structured organization. It serves as a hub for my learning journey, allowing me to curate and share knowledge while inviting you to follow along.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-a-learning-wiki-blog&quot;&gt;Why a Learning Wiki-Blog?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A learning wiki-blog offers several advantages:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Narrative Learning: I can share my learning experiences and insights in a storytelling format.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Structured Knowledge: Information is neatly organized, making it accessible and easy to navigate.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Community Engagement: It encourages interaction and collaboration, fostering a sense of shared learning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-to-expect&quot;&gt;What to Expect&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this dynamic space, you’ll find a wide range of learning topics and experiences:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Learning Logs: Personal reflections on what I'm studying, experimenting with, and discovering.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Knowledge Capsules: Summaries and explanations of intriguing concepts, theories, and ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Know-How Nuggets: Practical insights, tips, and guides on various skills and disciplines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;collaborate-and-enhance&quot;&gt;Collaborate and Enhance&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This personal wiki-blog is not just about my journey. It’s an open invitation for collaboration and collective growth. If you have insights, additional information, or suggestions to improve any of the articles, I wholeheartedly encourage you to contribute through pull requests. Together, we can enhance the depth and breadth of knowledge shared here, making it an even more valuable resource for everyone. Your contributions will not only enrich this platform but also leave a lasting imprint on the broader learning community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;embrace-the-software-engineering-odyssey&quot;&gt;Embrace the Software Engineering Odyssey&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this personal wiki-blog, I aim to embark on a captivating journey, where knowledge, tips, and considerations in the realm of software engineering and software principles take center stage. Together, we will explore the intricate landscape of code, algorithms, and best practices, all while delving into the ever-evolving world of software. My goal is to share insights, cultivate expertise, and ignite discussions that inspire growth and innovation. Thank you for joining me on this exhilarating software engineering odyssey, where the pursuit of knowledge is boundless, and the possibilities are endless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy coding and exploring!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Welcome to my personal wiki-blog, a dynamic platform where I document and share my ongoing learning process and my knowledge. In this article, I’d like to introduce you to this unique fusion of a personal blog and a wiki, designed to capture my educational adventures and growth.</summary></entry></feed>